I see. You're making an outfit for your school's contest.
Going with a suit?
We're gonna be working on this one as a team.
We're a team when we make Hina dolls, too.
It helps to split the workload.
It's not a solo gig?
Well, the tasks are typically divided.
Head, clothes, hands, props, hair.
And a different artisan puts together all the finishing touches.
At our shop, it takes approximately ten people to complete one Hina doll.
Whoa! That's a whole squad!
Multiple artists often work together on the same face.
Each feature is its own job.
That's seriously wild stuff.
So, like, how many Hina dolls do you apply makeup to in a day?
Usually it's around two to three hundred.
Stop. You're kidding, right?
On busy days, we'll do even more than that.
Painting those teeny tiny faces looks so impossible.
I would have guessed you guys only knock out like ten or so when you're super locked in.
Only ten?
We would never make our shipping deadlines.
I wasn't really going for funny.
The only reason we're able to do it is because we have lots of help.
Specialized work like this isn't the sort of thing you can do on your own.
It'll drive you nuts.
It may be easy to lend a friend a hand, but the ability to ask for help when you need it is a tricky skill to cultivate.
We must learn to rely on those around us.
Right.
Your girl needs seconds!
If you're booked up until the festival is over, I could do your laundry to save you some time.
That's okay. I don't want you to hurt your back again.
I'm fine. The doctor said it's as good as new.
I'm almost certain they didn't.
How did you know?
Hmm?
踏んだ風に誘われた坂道の向こう側に
広がる青。目に奪われて
おとおたって。ときめきの予感
真っ白な秘めた気持ちが色づいてゆく
最高は君と紡いていく未来
If you're still so blinding, but maybe
it's foam that comes first- WWII
It's the name ofDIX
It's a song that brings you to theCL
The importance of your URL
However life is found
It will keep going
Youcrit should be quiet
If you're speaking fast
ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON ON
Happy morning, Gojo!
Happy morning, Kitagawa.
Get enough sleep?
Yeah, I'm good.
Just had an early start is all.
I wanted to help, so I made you a little bento, or whatever.
You buy lunch at the school store, yeah?
It's always crowded, so to save you some time, I made it a little snacky for you.
Wow, such determination!
If Kitagawa is cooking, I know what that means.
Fried rice.
I'd at least like to know which kind.
It's a nice gesture, but I could be in for a world of hurt.
Say, I would love to know what you made.
Well, until we get to lunchtime, that's secret.
Come hungry, okay?
Okay.
And just like that, lunchtime had arrived.
The line for the store was literal madness.
To be totally transparent, this is my first attempt at making a bento.
I'm low-key freaking out right now.
That makes two of us.
It's a little funky, but please don't laugh.
Ta-da!
A spam on a giri sando!
So it's not fried rice surprise?
I wanted something you could eat quickly, so I landed on this bad boy.
Awesome!
It looks super delicious!
I-I'm sorry I was being so weird.
Just thinking about the bento you made me,
my heart felt like it was going to beat out of my chest!
Thank you so much!
His heart felt like it was beating out of his chest!
That means he was mega happy, right?
All that over my bento!
I could literally die!
This is a total surprise attack!
Way unfair, dude!
I love you so much!
I love you too much!
Every day I love you even more!
And it's gonna make me explode!
Almighty bento.
Thank you for this gift.
I'm so happy you're excited!
I've worked my literal butt cheeks off,
but I'll make you another one tomorrow!
It doesn't even matter!
You still gotta try it.
Here!
Thank you so much!
Hold on.
Why is it so heavy?
Hey, lunch buddy!
I slayed yesterday so hard,
I decided to cook some more!
Maureen's spam otagiri?
2.0!
Today's menu...
Karage skewers!
I worked hard today.
Meaty rice goodness.
This Buri Daikon is bomb!
I have to agree!
The mackerel miso you made us yesterday
was incredible too!
So are you on some kind of fish cooking kick right now?
You could say that.
I need seconds.
I'm always impressed with you, Maureen.
You have such a healthy appetite.
This belly never takes a break.
Hey, could I get you seconds too, Grandpa?
Sure, thank you.
You got it.
Here are the official deets.
The drag kings will perform first,
followed by the drag queens.
You'll have one minute to charm the audience.
A minute?
So short!
I mean, every single class participates.
If I want to charm them as Ray-sama...
Just do the champ call.
Oh!
Ooh!
It's way longer than I thought.
We're gonna have to shorten the heck out of this thing.
Cut the parts that mention champagne.
Hmm.
So, no getting crunk?
This is for a high school festival, not a real club.
Too bad.
WWRD?
If I were Ray-sama, I'd do this part.
Hmm?
You could do the call and response with boys from class.
Yeeees!
That.
I love it!
Genius call!
This is straight fire!
Hmm!
Let's replicate the lighting from the host club.
We are so freaking smart!
I'm getting so hyped up for this.
I can't wait to see Maureen as Ray-sama!
You're so obsessed with Ray.
It's kind of creepy.
Of course I am.
She makes you feel like a princess.
If only someone could treat me like that,
the bento scene killed me.
Yeah, same here.
After all that time, she shows Kouyumi her true self.
If a mysterious hottie revealed herself to me, of all people, I would fold like a lawn chair.
Did you pick up on the fact that it's the only time Ray-sama ever asked anyone for anything?
Will you make another?
I melt when she asks Kouyumi to make her another bento because it reminds her of her mom.
I wish Ray would ask me to do something.
The emotion of that scene makes volume 14 the best volume ever!
The day I got it, I read it 20 times,
and talking about it again now makes me want to be Ray-sama even more!
I just can't wait to see that moment come to life!
Being special in the eyes of someone everyone loves.
I get it.
Of course they like the bento scene.
I do too.
It's perfect.
You love that scene too, Kouyumi?
Sorry for eavesdropping!
Your fave character is Tsumugi, isn't it?
Uh, yeah.
Nice.
So you watched the entire anime?
That's quite a big feat.
Isn't the bento scene just the greatest?
Definitely.
But it took you talking about it for me to realize how amazing Ray-sama really is.
I guess I don't understand exactly how girls feel or exactly what Shoujo...
You're in too deep!
Even for us girls, it can be hard to relate to those princess-type characters.
That makes sense.
Their lives are pretty far removed from what we experience in the real world.
Hello there.
I'm Maureen.
It's a pleasure.
Is this your first time, princess?
I'm pretty certain I'm not a princess.
I'm helping you relate to Kouyumi, goober!
Can you handle your liquor, princess?
I've never had any, so I have no way of knowing.
Let's find out.
I'm drinking champagne.
You're a bra!
She's way too precious.
Don't forget about me, Maureen.
Come on.
I came all the way here because I missed you.
Fine.
How much can you spend?
I'm sorry.
I don't have much today.
Only 800 million.
Will that do?
I'd hope so!
And how much cash does my princess over here have to spend on me?
Gojo!
Champagne!
Got a second, man?
Of course!
Is there something I can help you with?
Yeah, we need a hand.
Think you can help bring this giant sign inside?
Mm-hmm.
Cool.
The interior design team wants to nail down a menu.
Okay.
Coming!
Uh-huh.
Noah, your hair looks really cute like that.
It should be your go-to style.
For reals?
Should we get fancy for the pageant?
Yes, and also, duh.
Until then.
Through chat.
It's done unless you're leased.
You're doing your thinking.
Bum, what's he doing?
I'm doing her.
Thank you.
Alright, let's now.
Thanks.
Bye-bye.
Hey there.
Yeah? What's up?
Not much. They just want to practice the champagne call, so they need you in the classroom.
Great! Sounds epic! I'll head there now!
Bye-bye!
Sorry. I promise I'll fix it right after this, okay?
Huh?
Please, leave it!
Champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne, champagne.
Looks like Kitagawa tried to sew on a button.
She messed it up.
Huh.
Tomorrow, I'm going to have her try on her outfit.
Since suits are new to me, I hope that everything fits okay.
Other people pull them off.
Looking through these again, I wonder how so many women achieve that masculine look.
Last time I worked on a crossplay, this magazine gave me makeup and body shaping tips.
It says all that I have to do is line my breasts up with the cups, fasten the hooks, and smooth everything out.
Slowly lift up, holding the center of the front and back, lift over your hips.
What the hell?
Sorcery!
These babies are literally magical!
Your girl is gone, Pancake!
This is intense, Maureen.
I never thought about how much work cosplay takes.
Don't you get sweaty and tired?
My passion for these characters and the desire to be them outweighs all that junk.
But this dude's stuff is a lot.
Didn't know until I tried.
The verdict is...
Yay!
The quality is crazy!
You just became Rei-sama.
I even watched parts of the sewing process, and I'm still totally floored!
It's kind of scary how awesome you are at this, Gojo.
You're so tall!
The insoles are working overtime!
That fabric is to die for.
Usami actually picked it out for us.
So, uh...
Please be honest.
We're not done yet.
The suit's too big, isn't it?
I didn't think so.
Pardon me.
Pardoned.
I'm pretty sure it should fit like this.
Ooh!
That totally captures Rei-sama's essence!
It's a tiny tweak, but it makes all the difference!
I didn't account for any shapewear when I first sized the suit!
I messed up.
I'll fix it.
Huh?
Well, if I leave it, then it won't be accurate.
Are you sure you have time for all that?
I swear I'll get it done before the pageant.
Okie doke.
You're really redoing it?
It's so damn good!
What a waste!
Gojo, so you're fixing the top and the bottoms?
And the bottoms?
Madness!
Before that, I'd like to try something.
No matter how perfect your facial expressions are, they'll be hard to see from far away.
And in the interview section, you won't be able to hold the same face.
You'll have the suit and the makeup, but there's one other thing I'd like you to try to look more masculine.
I think it could really help sell the character.
The whole time Himeno was in cosplay, he held himself like a woman.
It may seem trivial, but the way you act will change how everyone sees you.
You're right.
Amane was totes a girl.
Who's this Amane person?
So cute!
College student Amane Himeno.
Whoa!
Please, Kitagoa!
Introduce me like right now!
I can, but just so you know, he's a dude.
It's over!
Get a grip.
I've never seen someone get their heart broken that fast.
I need to be more manly, right?
Uh, yeah.
Man me up!
We must learn to rely on those around us.
Huh?
Morita?
Uh…
The way you move is so confident and cool.
It's masculine without even trying.
If you could…
I'd appreciate it if you'd help her out.
Kitsugawa!
You are my pupil now!
Welcome to the school of being manly and…
You are so annoying!
No fighting, team.
Please lighten up, you two.
Like this?
Keep your feet shoulder-width apart and point your toes out a little.
Stand up straight, stick out your chest slightly, and tuck in your chin.
How's this?
You're so cool!
You instantly turned into a guy from the neck down.
Nah, I'm a good teacher.
Eat my suit.
Whoa!
So the fit is all done!
You are so annoying!
No fighting, team.
Please lighten up, you two.
Like this?
Keep your feet shoulder-width apart and point your toes out a little.
Stand up straight, stick out your chest slightly, and tuck in your chin.
How's this?
You're so cool!
You instantly turned into a guy from the neck down.
Nah, I'm a good teacher.
Eat my suit.
Whoa!
So the fit is all done!
You're a damn genius!
Gojo is a sewing wizard!
Shazam!
Here, these are from Hana-chan.
Arigato, Takaru-kun!
Thank you.
Murakami!
Get in here already!
He's been waiting to come see you for a while.
Shut up, you dumbass!
Don't tell them that!
Dude, what's your problem?
I was trying to be chill.
They might think I'm a creep for liking the series.
It's embarrassing enough that you guys heard me nerd out over the drama the other day.
That isn't something you should be embarrassed about.
So it's normal?
Yeah, of course!
It's the kind of show that has something for everybody!
As for your nerding out, that just means you've got the strong connection!
I mean, I watch the drama too.
Yeah, but you weren't holding the remote.
Maybe you're right.
I mean...
Screw it!
Sorry, but can I get a quick picture?
I want to tell my sister that my friend made Rei's suit.
Major bragging rights.
Uh, yeah!
I'd be honored!
Thanks, man!
Maureen, do that sick pose you just mastered.
Roger!
Whoa!
This is crazy!
You erased someone in the flesh!
The mind is blown!
Thanks, Kitagawa!
How dare you cut off my head!
No question that you're hardcore, bro.
While you're here, check out all the details.
Maybe I need one more picture.
Another picture.
Bye,fterikawa!
Love you ice.
What are you additionally in for the future?
The tyle?
It's terrible.
dunno, so anime m jeszcze nple lovelace.
Ye out.
Love you did withiri Mirai.
I gotta make my fundraising.
What are you done?
I did queen!
It's beautiful!
Thank you.